NANPU BRIDGE
OUTPATIENT
SEVEN DAYS AGO
You are good.
When you're in the operating room,
just keep blabbering.
Doctor, minimally invasive
gallbladder removal
isn't that dangerous, right?
Our surgical technology
is very mature now,
but everyone has a different constitution.
I still suggest that Zhuang Jie
rest and recuperate after surgery.
But with this profession of ours,
how can I keep her in Shanghai?
Well…
But don't worry.
I'll do everything I can
to persuade her to go home
and rest and recuperate there.
That's right.
She can treat it as a vacation.
A vacation?
This is my first vacation
ever since I joined the workforce.
But since Wang Xixia, my hometown friend,
colleague, and best friend,
has already
made the necessary arrangement,
I'll have no choice but to oblige.
I've lived in Shanghai for many years.
My hometown, Nanping,
isn't as familiar to me.
I only remember that it is a town
that is beside mountains and the ocean.
There are 18 administrative villages
and 26 natural villages.
The total population is 390,000.
There are listed pharmaceutical factories,
electrical appliance factories,
and porcelain factories
with revenue growth year after year.
I heard
that the tourism sector was growing too.
On the business streets
where influencers often check in,
there is a stunning view.
That is
Ms. Liao Tao's braised chicken shop!
LIAOGEN BRAISED CHICKEN
Liao Tao?
You guys have seen her before.
She's my mom.
This woman whose mood changes rapidly
and doesn't mean what she says
got married to Mr. He
with me and Zhuang Yan
when she was 35 years old.
Mr. He is my dad's old comrade.
He doesn't speak much and is very kind.
To us,
he's the best stepdad in the world.
Especially when the sensitive Zhuang Yan
gradually became a thorn in my mom's eyes.
As the lubricant of the family,
Mr. He is an important member.
When Ms. Liao Tao was 40,
she gave birth to my sister, He Niaoniao.
She's just like a spring breeze.
She brought endless laughter
to me and Zhuang Yan.
However, she also brought endless trouble
to my mom and Mr. He.
However,
even my family members don't know
that there's one individual in Nanping
who left a deep impression on me.
Although we haven't met for many years,
and his personality
is still as eccentric as ever,
I'm still happy
to be able to reunite with him.
That individual is
Chen Maidong.
Grandma.
As for this…
Isn't this Ms. Lin's expertise?
You!
Stop interrupting me.
I'm already frustrated enough.
If you ask me if they are fated,
I don't think they are merely fated.
Maybe there is
a deeper bond between them.
A deeper bond?
ADAPTED FROM THE ORIGINAL WORK
"LOVER" BY SHE MU SI
My son!
You were only 17!
The cops and medical examiner just left.
Confirmed accidental drowning
while swimming.
It has been more than 36 hours.
That child was only 17.
He argued with his parents a few days ago.
They thought that he was living
at his classmate's house.
That's why they didn't look for him.
My son!
Please accept our condolences.
We're from Nanping Funeral Parlor.
Leave your child to us.
We'll make the necessary arrangements.
Please don't worry.
-Let's go.
-My son!
My son!
Let's go.
Have you prepared
the gurney and the hearse?
The road was hard to traverse.
We only arrived not long ago.
Did that kid discover the victim?
Yes. I think it's the kid we saw
in the restaurant yesterday.
He's in shock.
Even ordinary folks can't stand
the sight of a waterlogged corpse.
Reconfirm it.
Is your name Zhuang Yan?
We're going to take his body back.
Are you okay?
Do you want us to notify
your family members to pick you up?
Where are you guys taking him?
To my workplace.
We'll see him off on his last journey.
I'll go as well.
May I?
Only family members
are allowed to observe the rites.
Just let me stay there for a while.
Please.
Xilun,
take him to my car.
Please follow me.
Jie.
Sorry. Please stop here.
Let me take a breather.
Xilun, head back first.
Okay, Master.
You can sit here and take a break.
I might be very busy later.
I may not have time to tend to you.
I'm very sorry
that you received such a shock.
That boy is around my age, right?
He was supposed
to take the NCEE next year.
What's his name?
Trust me.
No matter how much you know about him,
it won't help you
in alleviating your negative emotions.
I always thought
that things with names
contain a soul.
I'm sure he has a great name too.
One such that his parents
expected great things from him.
Maybe they hoped that he would
become someone extraordinary.
Or maybe they hoped
that he would live a long life in peace.
Jie,
that boy's life
hasn't even started yet.
He didn't even get to realize his dreams,
and he's gone just like that.
He didn't live a glorious life
or have a memorial tablet
erected after him.
Soon,
no one in this world will remember him
except for his parents.
What's the point
of a life like that?
To humans, death is the most helpless,
yet fairest event in our lives.
The weight of one's ash
weighs between 1,800 g to 3,100 g.
Whether one was successful or not
doesn't matter.
It's already meaningful
as long as they have existed before.
Yan,
have you not heard of this saying before?
Sometimes, misfortunes
do haunt good people too.
I think you'll be able to understand
if you just look at me.
Someone once told me…
Even a crutch can be used as a weapon.
"Even a crutch can be used as a weapon."
I believed him.
That's why I'm doing pretty well now.
Humans are very resilient.
No matter if it's you
or the parents of that child,
everyone will get over it.
I have to resume my work.
You guys should head back soon.
Come on, let's go home.
Thank you.
Is Zhuang Yan asleep?
He took half of a sleeping pill.
He finally fell asleep.
Who told him to go to that remote area
instead of staying at home?
That's enough.
Zhuang Yan didn't want
to encounter that either.
Stop pulling a long face.
I just think that he's too fragile
as a man.
Look at him.
He's scared witless.
He Niaoniao was the one
who found his pet for him.
The coroner already said
that the bloated corpse
was a disturbing sight.
Everyone has to take some time off
after seeing that.
Besides, you shouldn't
just keep talking about gender.
Who said that boys shouldn't cry
or be afraid?
You're being sexist here.
You always side with your brother.
Everything is my fault.
You said he was reliable.
The only thing he's good at
is taking exams.
He hasn't contributed
a single cent for the family yet,
and now, he wants to quit school.
It's just a thought.
Don't jump to conclusions yet.
Let's take a step back.
All roads lead to Rome.
Rome?
If he can still rule over Nanping
after quitting school,
I'll kneel and kowtow to him.
How long does it take to cook this?
You should sleep earlier.
I think you're easily irritated
due to lack of sleep.
Stop trying to analyze me.
Do you think I want to stand here
and cook all night?
I had enough of this long ago.
I would've rented a factory building
in the developmental zone last year
if it weren't for you guys.
Everything would be automated.
I wouldn't need to go through all of this.
That's great.
I fully support this notion of yours.
Rent it?
Do you expect me to sell my kidneys?
My savings and Mr. He's savings
were all used up
to buy houses for you three.
Did you buy houses?
Did you buy one for me too?
Aren't you my daughter?
Of course you have to be included.
Mom, I already told you long ago.
I won't return to this town.
Even if you did buy it,
you should rent it out.
Didn't you say
that all roads lead to Rome?
The main focus is the road and Rome,
not the countryside and Nanping.
What?
Do you want to talk
about the inner world with me as well?
Is Shanghai your Rome?
Is this town too small for you?
That's not what I mean.
What do you mean, then? Tell me.
Tell me.
My son is useless
while my daughters make me worry.
I…
I wonder why I'm working so hard!
Didn't I tell you to be frugal at home?
So what if you're trendy?
No one is looking at you.
Wear the anti-slip slippers
that He made for you.
What?
You should tell me if you're out of money.
Your son isn't earning money,
but your daughter earns a lot.
I don't want your money.
What? Are you favoring your son
over your daughter now?
You can only depend on your son
to continue your bloodline.
Are you afraid
of owing your daughter a favor
when she is trying to give you money?
No one in this town
can win an argument against you three.
Mom,
I love to stay beside you and Mr. He.
It's very comfortable.
But it's too comfortable.
It'll polish my determination away.
I can stay here for a short while.
But I cannot stay here
for the rest of my life.
I have to strive to improve myself
because I'm physically disabled.
Ever since I got into university
in Shanghai, I had decided
that I must be more determined
than ordinary people.
I'm going to be Nanping's pride and joy.
I'll spread my roots in Shanghai.
I'm going
to climb higher and higher
so that I can see
the beautiful view up there.
LIAOGEN CHICKEN
Here. Thank you.
Okay.
One chicken, right?
Liao Tao, hurry up!
Fill out this form for me.
Where did you come from?
You're sweating so much.
Because I'm tied up in official duties.
The mayor intends
to gather all the undergraduates
who are studying or working
in other cities
for a tea party
during the Labor Day holiday.
I've been finding them
one household after another
to complete the census.
When I reached your household,
I couldn't find
Zhuang Yan's household information.
Look. This is so frustrating.
It has been so many years.
Just tell him to fill it out again.
Look at what you're saying.
I need to check
and update all these profiles every year.
Do you think this is
about missing information?
It's an insult to my professionalism!
This is so infuriating.
I have to say, menopause is terrible!
Nothing goes right
and I can't stop eating.
Sometimes, I even hate myself.
Me too.
This has nothing to do with menopause.
If anyone is to blame, blame Zhuang Yan.
Nothing goes well when he is involved.
Why are you blaming him for it?
What has this got to do with that child?
You're lucky
that you don't have a son like him.
One look at him
will cost you ten years of life.
No one is perfect.
You should be grateful
that you have a great daughter.
Just now, I saw Zhuang Jie
bringing He Niaoniao
to shop for clothes for you and He.
How could they be the same?
Zhuang Jie suffered together with me
since she was young.
I don't want her to suffer anymore.
Didn't you buy a house in town
for her in secret?
That's if she appreciates it.
She even talked back last night.
If I must say,
with that leg of hers and her vigor,
she won't find a husband easily
in Shanghai.
Don't worry.
You can leave this to me
as long as she's willing to come back.
Stop bragging.
You should deal with that pesky Mrs. Chen
before you say anything else.
My goodness.
Mrs. Chen is truly something else.
Now the entire town committee avoids her
when they see her.
In my opinion,
I think the girl
who marries into her family
must be the unluckiest girl in the world.
Sometimes,
I sympathize with Chen Maidong.
Jie, I'll improve my grades
by myself, okay?
Just leave me alone.
Hurry up.
Jie, are you taking me
to sign up for cram school?
I won't waste my money on that.
But I found a better way
for you to get lessons.
But Jie!
Shut up. No negotiations allowed.
Jie?
Mrs. Chen!
Where are you going?
I was planning
to buy some food from your shop
since I wasn't cooking tonight.
Go ahead. My mom is there.
I'll tell her to give you a discount.
Consider it as a thank you
to Chen Maidong
for taking care of Zhuang Yan.
No need for that.
Indeed.
From now on,
we should help each other
since we're a family.
What do you mean by "we're a family"?
That means
your sister, Zhuang Jie,
and my grandson, Chen Maidong,
are destined to get married.
You see,
no one can avoid their fate.
You must've lost your mind.
Wait.
Come here.
Jie,
don't blame me for being frank.
Both of you are adults now.
There's nothing to be shy about.
I've done divination for you two.
Ma'am, we don't believe in superstition.
All right, then.
Let's talk about it objectively.
Are you single?
You are about the same age as Maidong.
And you two
know each other pretty well, right?
That settles it, then.
Look at him. He's handsome.
You're very beautiful.
There's no reason for you two
not to be with each other.
Mrs. Chen,
thank you for taking a liking to me.
To be honest,
I did have feelings for your grandson.
Back in high school,
I thought Chen Maidong was pretty nice.
But it was so long ago.
Scientists said that human cells
are renewed once every seven years.
Now we're totally different.
I don't have feelings for him.
He's like a stranger to me.
That's even better.
Get to know each other again.
It'll be fun!
I came back to Nanping for vacation.
I'll be returning to Shanghai soon.
Chen Maidong and I
can only be friends.
I mustn't ruin his future.
Thanks.
Hey!
Jie, listen to me.
I'm not lying!
You two are truly destined to be together!
Thanks.
Thanks, my foot.
Let's go!
Grandma, that's the second time.
Can you please stop embarrassing me
in front of other people?
Zhuang Jie and I aren't close.
Stay out of this.
Grandma.
Be honest with me.
Have I ever tried this hard
to help you court a girl before this?
Why did you have to pick Zhuang Jie?
Did Ms. Lin put a spell over you?
Don't slander her.
Lin has been teaching me
how to recite poems lately.
Recite poems?
That sounds scary.
What kinds of poems?
Chen Maidong,
you're overstepping your boundaries.
Do you think you can test me now?
I dare not do so.
I just wish to translate it for you.
Maybe I can make up a version
that's unrelated to Zhuang Jie.
Heaven's secrets are not to be divulged.
I've already made up my mind.
Since you're not doing it yourself,
I'm casting away my pride
to court Jie on your behalf.
Grandma.
Grandma!
Can you stop messing around?
Fine.
I'll give you a second choice.
Tell your parents to come here.
Have them bring their spouses
and family members.
We'll hold an official family meeting
and talk about your personal issues.
There's no need to resort to that.
Now you know
the definition of messing around.
Fine.
I'll consider it seriously.
Kid,
I assume your skills in picking up girls
haven't grown rusty yet, right?
I never had that skill in the first place.
All the girls court me.
Cocky, aren't you?
I dare you to be cocky again!
Brat!
This time, He Niaoniao really is studying.
Her whiteboard looked full.
Really?
Really.
Is that class monitor of hers a wizard?
Did he change the nature
of an underachiever in one afternoon?
Teach students
according to their aptitude.
He Niaoniao likes cute guys.
Her class monitor is upright and handsome.
Of course she'll study hard
if he tutors her.
Great job.
The thing is, why did he agree to it?
Zhuang Jie,
did you do something drastic again?
You're the best
at belittling your children.
If He Niaoniao wants to please someone,
no one in the world can stop her.
Do you think being witty alone
could make this work?
She must've spent a lot of money.
Of course I couldn't be empty-handed.
I bought him some tonics.
But that's not what he was after.
He's mainly grateful to me
for getting a checkup for his grandpa
at the provincial hospital
at an insider's price.
Look at her.
Nowadays, you have to go so far
just to please someone.
You know nothing.
You think that you can survive
just by carrying an art canvas around.
You won't sell any paintings
if you don't have social skills.
I have Jie.
She can promote even He Niaoniao.
I'm sure she can sell my paintings.
Madam Wu wants you to go
to the mayor's tea party tomorrow.
Tell me whether you're going or not.
I don't have social skills.
Tell Jie to go on my behalf.
Fine, I'll go.
Zhuang Yan, keep up the momentum.
Monitor He Niaoniao's studies.
Okay.
What? You're being so sneaky.
Yan, you now have two choices.
Either you sit here as an audience
or join me in solving this issue.
I choose neither.
You must be up to no good again.
-Mom.
-Yan!
Yan.
I assume you don't know him.
What makes you think so?
This is Maidong.
He's an outstanding person.
Has he won your heart too
in just a few days?
What do you mean by that?
Where did you find out all this about him?
Jie must not get together
with Chen Maidong.
Why?
It's because Jie
let her tongue slip today.
I did have feelings for your grandson.
But it was so long ago.
What?
Isn't it peculiar?
Both of us were kept in the dark.
You almost had me duped.
I was only four when Jie was transferred
to the high school here.
You weren't even born yet.
You don't know anything.
That's not the point here.
The thing is, our sister was always frank.
Why has she never
mentioned her first love?
First love?
Why are you jumping to conclusions?
Yan, they've had a peculiar relationship
since high school.
All high schoolers and middle schoolers
knew about it.
Why was it so well-known?
It was because they didn't
suit each other.
Anyway, I have plenty of reason
to suspect that Chen Maidong
has been in Jie's heart all these years.
He's using psychic powers
to gaslight our sister,
causing her to remain single until now.
HONGXU CARGO TERMINAL
-Pass.
-I don't have any.
-None?
-Who dealt these hands?
He's here.
Six!
Why don't you join us?
You're finally free today.
Go.
-Six.
-Nine.
Ten.
Circle.
Joker of diamonds.
Joker of spades.
My turn.
-Pass.
A pair of eights.
Are you hiding out
because your grandma whooped your butt?
Shut up.
Maidong,
why did I hear
that your grandma
stopped a girl in public?
There's no use staring at me.
Our town is so tiny.
It takes two hours for gossip to spread.
Just don't spread it to me.
Do you know who his grandma
stopped in public?
Who was it?
Zhuang Jie.
The girl who transferred
to our high school
who can't walk properly.
Her?
Enough.
I saw her on the streets two days ago.
She looked like a normal person to me.
The medical technology of modern cities
is amazing indeed.
You don't say?
I didn't dare to speak with her
when I saw her leg in the past.
It felt as if she was very depressed.
Change the topic.
Let's change the topic.
Four.
Six.
Now, Zhuang Jie
is totally different.
Standing in a crowd,
she's eye-catching.
She's beautiful.
It's no wonder his grandma
is obsessed with her.
I told you to change the topic!
Chen Maidong, don't push your luck.
Right now, we feel the same
as your grandma.
When you were in high school,
you were well-known as a rich man's son
with a terrible temper and strong fists.
But now?
He's left on the shelf!
What's going on?
If I must say, you should rekindle
your past relationship
with Zhuang Jie.
Rekindle, my foot.
You were the ones who spread the rumor.
Who said so?
We dare not do so.
You see…
-there's no smoke without fire.
-There's no smoke without fire.
No smoke without fire, right?
What? Let's talk this over.
Don't get violent.
Chen Maidong, you act decent at work.
Why do you act like a thug
when you come here?
Should I state the obvious?
Go ahead.
If you don't have a good point,
I'll make sure you learn your lesson!
Stop! What are you doing?
Chen Maidong!
You know full well
how that scandal with Zhuang Jie started.
Back then, you were a total fool.
How could you fall under the control
of an unremarkable disabled girl?
Quiet down.
You are participating in a play,
not the circus.
You'll lose your voice
if you keep this up.
Let's take a picture.
By the way, miss,
we still need two more trees.
I thought Song Wei and Li Yang
were supposed to be the trees.
They don't want to do it
because trees have no lines
and wanted to be guards instead.
Then…
Zhuang Jie,
are you willing to participate
and make some fun high school memories
along the way?
But don't force yourself
if you're afraid it's too much for you.
I'm in.
But
we need two trees, right?
One tree will do.
The main point is your participation.
What about Chen Maidong?
He doesn't have a role either.
He and I
will be the two trees.
Chen Maidong.
It's rare for Zhuang Jie
to participate in an event.
Stop pretending to be sick.
You two can play the trees together, okay?
Fine.
Take a few more pictures.
ALL ANIMALS IN THIS PROGRAM
WERE TREATED KINDLY